Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- Audiovisual Materials, 1983-1998; 1983 1998; 40 linear feet
  - Miscellaneous Recordings, 1983-1997
    - Lecture: Dr. Ekers, 25 Nov. 1986 (Oversizebox 8.014)
    - Rosenblith, Dr. Walter A., "Science: An International Endeavor," (3 cassettes), 9 Dec. 1986 (Oversizebox 8.022)
    - Perper, 19 Dec. 1986 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Duncan, R., F. Rossini, John Barach, Bany Lichter, 7 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Pievsall, Dr. George, James S. McKnight, 9 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Wagner, Kenneth, Almargeev Kaul, Eileen Fanelli, 13-14 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - O'Leary, James, Judy Miller, David Dibiasio, 14-15 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Bopp, Lawrence Ken Armitage, Charles Rodenberger, Tony J. Pederle, 24 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - San Antonio Workshop (3 cassettes), 24 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - San Antonio Workshop, Ken Yasukawa, 24 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - San Antonio Workshop, 25 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - San Antonio Workshop, Alston Chase, 25 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Lacewell, Ron George Teetus Louise Canfield-Sander, Glen Williams, 30 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Matthewson, Dr. Chris, Dr. Grita Fryxell, 30 Jan. 1987 (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Multidisciplinary Science, 3 Apr. 1987 (Oversizebox 8.014)
    - Science and Technology Day, 1989 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Forum on Global Change and Our Common Future, Keynote Address by Norway Prime Minister MME. Gro Harlem Brundtland (2 cassettes), 2 May 1989 (Oversizebox 8.014)
    - Lecture: Maxey, Dr. Margaret, 17 May 1989 (Oversizebox 8.014)
    - Focus Group: University of Texas at Austin (3 tapes), 22-24 May 1990 (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Meeting, Calspan Chapter, 8 Nov. 1990 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Global Change and the Human Prospect (5 cassettes), 13-15 Aug. 1991 (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Conference Call, Sep. 1991 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - The Scientific Research Society Mayaguez Club Presents: Dr. Lawrence M. Krauss, "The Beginning and End of the Universe", 25 Nov. 1991 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Ethical Issues in Scientific Research, 11 Nov. 1992 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Meeting (3 cassettes), 16 Jan. 1993 (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Assembly of Delegates, 26 Feb. 1993 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Meeting, 28 Feb. 1993 (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Conference Call, 12 Oct. 1993 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Conference Call, 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Conference Call, 6 Jan. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Meeting (4 cassettes), 15 Jan. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Meeting, 15 Apr. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Workshop, 16 Apr. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Focus Group (2 cassettes), 25 Jun. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Focus Group: Chicago Academy of Sciences (2 cassettes), 6 Aug. 1994 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee Meeting (2 cassettes), 13-14 Jan. 1995 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Committee on Membership: Meeting (2 tapes), 14 Jan. 1995 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Avila (2 cassettes), 25-26 Jul. 1995 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Global Change Networks (2 cassettes), 26 Jul. 1995 (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - North Carolina State University/Engineering Research, Raw Footage Segments, 1 Nov. 1995 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Committee on Membership: Meeting (3 cassettes), 17 Feb. 1996 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Breakthrough: The Changing Face of Science in America, 15 Apr. 1996 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - O.M.E.D. D.C. Parent Meeting, 28 Jun. 1996 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Committee on Science and Society: Meeting, 8 Mar. 1997 (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Unidentified, 8 May 1997 (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Focus Group: UI (2 cassettes), 24-25 May (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - AAS, undated (Cassettebox 8.006)
    - Asilomar (5 cassettes), undated (Cassettebox 8.006)
    - Business Session, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Cambel, Ali, Sorrows, John Higginson, undated (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Conversations From Wingspread: Science and Society: Acid Rain/Robotics, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Conversations From Wingspread: Science and Society: Genetics and Human Heredity/Ethics and Science, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Conversations From Wingspread: Science and Society: Short Segments, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Conversations From Wingspread: Scientific Literacy/Understanding Science, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - DPA Environmental Issues, undated (Oversizebox 8.022)
    - Eisner Proctor Prize (2 cassettes), undated (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Focus Group: Dallas, undated (Cassettebox 8.007)
    - Focus Group: Duke, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - International Committee: Retreat (2 cassettes), undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - International Cooperation in Technology Development, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - International Space Station, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Jr. Sciences Symposium Panel Discussion, undated (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - Meeting, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Multidisciplinary Science (2 cassettes), undated (Oversizebox 8.015)
    - "Multidisciplinary Science" (2 cassettes), undated (Oversizebox 8.022)
    - Question and Answer on Mapping the Human Genome, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Reynolds, George, Leonard Liggio, undated (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Successful Innovation Strategies in Small and Medium Size Companies, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Teleconference: Allocating Federal Funds for Science and Technology, undated (Oversizebox 8.016)
    - Teleconference: Carbon Dioxide, undated (Oversizebox 8.016)
    - The Science and Politics of Large Scale International Collaborations, undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Tullock, Gordon, undated (Cassettebox 8.024)
    - Ulysses/Shair, undated (Oversizebox 8.016)
    - Unlabeled (7 cassettes), undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - Unlabeled (2 cassettes), undated (Oversizebox 8.016)
    - Unlabeled (2 cassettes), undated (Oversizebox 8.022)
    - Unlabeled (3 cassettes), undated (Box 8.023)
    - Weapons of Mass Destruction (2 cassettes), undated (Cassettebox 8.008)
    - World According to Weisskoph, undated (Oversizebox 8.022)